perfectconnectiongolfswing.com 2013-05-21

# Perfect Connection Golf Swing Privacy Policy

**PRIVACY POLICY**

**(Last Revised: October 10, 2012)**

Thank you for visiting this web site. We understand the importance that Internet users place on privacy, and this Privacy Policy describes how we use personal information that is collected at this web site. Please read this Privacy Policy before using this site or submitting any personal information. By using this web site, you accept the privacy practices contained in this Privacy Policy. These privacy practices may change from time to time, but any changes will be posted. You are encouraged to review the Privacy Policy whenever you visit the web site to make sure you understand how any personal information you provide will be used.

**Information We Collect**

In order to serve our customers, we collect personally identifiable information, like names, addresses, phone numbers, email addresses, and sometimes credit card information when such information is voluntarily submitted by our visitors. We will only use your personal information for the following purposes: (1) to deliver the products and/or services to you that you have requested; (2) to validate your compliance with the terms and conditions; (3) for content improvement and feedback purposes; and (4) to reach you, when necessary, regarding your use of the web site or product(s). 

We will NEVER share your information with third parties unless you have given us explicit permission to do so, such as in order to fulfill a third party offer that you have accepted from us. By permitting us to collect this information, you will be able to receive free information on products and services that may be of interest to you, including related third party offers that we may send to you. You also enable us to personalize your experience with us so that we can provide you with the highest quality of service. By submitting your email address on this web site, you agree to receive email from us. You can cancel your participation in any of these email lists at any time by clicking the opt-out link or other unsubscribe option that is included in the respective email. We only send emails to people who have authorized us to contact them, either directly, or through a third party. We do not send unsolicited commercial emails, because we hate spam as much as you do.

In addition, you agree that by submitting your email address on this web site and/or registering to receive the product and/or service offered herein, such act constitutes a purchase, an inquiry, and/or an application for the purposes of the Amended Telemarketing Sales Rule (ATSR), 16 CFR ‘310 et seq. and any applicable state and local “do not call” regulations. We retain the right to contact you via telemarketing in accordance with the ATSR and the applicable state regulations. 

**Third Party Actions**

We do not control and are not liable for the actions of any third parties who we may promote. We pride ourselves in working with quality companies, but have no control over the actions of those third parties. While we are not liable for any of the actions of those third parties, you should feel free to give us feedback from time to time on your experiences with any third parties to whom we work with so that we may enhance our future service to all customers.

**Cookies**

We may use cookies to deliver content that is specific to your interests. Cookies are text files that are used by your computer’s web browser to store your preferences, and enable us to enhance your user experience with our web site. 

**What are cookies?**

A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a user's computer for record-keeping purposes. We use cookies on this site. We do not link the information we store in cookies to any personally identifiable information you submit while on our site. We use both session ID cookies and persistent cookies. We use session cookies to make it easier for you to navigate our site. A session ID cookie expires when you close your browser. A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive for an extended period of time. You can remove persistent cookies by following directions provided in your Internet browser's "help" file.

Persistent cookies enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site.

Third party vendors, including Google, show our ads on sites on the internet. 

Third party vendors, including Google, use our cookies to serve CJH Interactive Sports LLC dba PerfectConnection Golf Swing ads based on a user's prior visits to our website. 

Users may opt out of Google's use of cookies by visiting the [Google advertising opt-out page](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html). (Alternatively you can opt out of a third party vendor's use of our cookies by visiting the [Network Advertising Initiative opt out page](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).)

**How can I disable the display of CJH Interactive Sports LLC dba PerfectConnection Golf Swing personalized advertisements?**

If you no longer want to be exposed to CJH Interactive Sports LLC dba PerfectConnection Golf Swing personalized banners, you can opt out by simply visiting the Network Advertising Initiative website: <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>.

**Please note:** This procedure will not block ads that are displayed on the websites you visit.

**Please note:** This opt out relies on a cookie, so if you wipe all your cookies then we will no longer know that you have opted out.

**Please note:** when you opt-out in this manner, a cookie will be set on your browser. We must maintain the cookie on your browser in order to recognize you as an opted-out visitor. You must opt-out again if you clear that cookie from your browser, use a different internet browser, or use a new computer to access the internet.

**IP Addresses**

We may use your IP address to help prevent fraud, to help diagnose problems with our server, to gather broad demographic information, and to offer you products and services.

**Third Party Web Sites**

This web site and/or the products and/or services offered herein may direct you to web sites that are owned and/or controlled by third parties. We have no control over those third parties and are not responsible for the content or the privacy practices of those sites or companies.

**Commitment to Data Security**

All information collected from you is stored in a technically and physically secure environment. We use SSL encryption to protect sensitive information online, and we do everything we can to protect user information offline. Unfortunately, no transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we take reasonable measures to protect your information, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of the information that you transmit to us, and you do so at your own risk.

**Contacting Us**

If you need to contact us, you can email us at Support@PerfectConnectionGolfSwing.com, call us at 877-228-7088, or send us a letter at: 100 Crescent Court #1200, Dallas, TX 75201.

We strive to provide excellent products, along with equally excellent customer service. If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or our practices, please feel free to contact us using one of the methods listed above.
